<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>Lust (YamikaDesu)</name>
    <directory>lust (yamikadesu)</directory>
    <id>3418387476</id>
    <description>Furry Character Mod made by YamikaDesu

The character's name is Lust (not to be confused with the boss Lust xD), he just wants hugs and cuddles so he will go around the basement spreading love with his whip! The character initially has the Crown of Light and flies, although it seems a bit broken it has been balanced (and will continue to be done) to make the character fun and difficult to play at the same time! He is also a melee character that uses an energy whip to attack enemies and synergizes with a lot of items. I hope you like it! He is also so cute! 

v1.1 : Just in case, there are some synergies that are a little more difficult to find, for example Spoon Bender provides homing tears but if you only have that item you won't be able to see its effect obviously, you can appreciate its effect when you synergize with another item such as example Tough Love since this item is modified in this mod making that the enemies release teeth when hit, so if you also have Spoon Bender then those teeth will be homing! You can try to create curious synergies and let me know if you have any suggestions! ^^

v1.2 : From v1.2 there is now a small chance (initially 5% that increases to a maximum of 50% with 10 Luck) that hits made on enemies will cause them to release tears from pain, these tears will have the properties of Lust's tears, so now items that added tear properties will be useful even if there are no additional items like Tough Love. The spawned tear will not damage the enemy from where it spawned!

v1.4 : A new mechanic has been added for Birthright, now taking it will create an aura around Lust that will allow him to give kisses to enemies making them become his allies (in the case of bosses the kisses will hurt them) the aura disappears if Lust receives damage (Crown of Light), will you be able to do a pacifist run with Birthright spreading love and hugs?

The sprites have been drawn by https://x.com/Freezepop88

The cover art has been drawn by Yaku

And the trailer video and cover gif has been made by https://x.com/Moshi_Shian 

If you find any bug or mod suggestion don't hesitate to comment it!</description>
    <version>1.9</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
</metadata>
